Historical Materials Collection UA136
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 1819 -- 2009; UA136.002; 4.6 Linear Feet; 1 Artifact(s); 1412 Digital Object(s)
  - Jackson College graduating class of, 1946; UA136.002.DO.01148; Unknown (Box Shared 106)
    (left to right) top row: Regina M. Lentino, Ruth D. Bloy, Virginia L. Priest, Edna O. Stiles/ middle row: Shirley Brown, Mrs. David W. Riley, Nancy A. Potter, Stella Fentzos/ bottom row: Laura S. Hayward, Nancy L. Nelson, Bessie Kalafatas, and Barbara Davis
  - Journalism class, 1941; UA136.002.DO.01149; Shearer Photography (Box Shared 106)
  - Students singing on campus, 1967; UA136.002.DO.01151; Unknown (Box Shared 106)
    Ed Silvers, Carolyn Bacher, Lynette Davis, Margaret Arlin, Dave Conners
  - Students on campus, 1969; UA136.002.DO.01152; Duette (Box Shared 106)
  - The Mess Hall, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01154; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
    6x8
    photographic print; Student Army Training Corps
  - Saturday morning inspection of troops, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01155; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
    Lieut. Burns, Lieut Sullivan, Major Bowman
    World War, 1914-1918; Buildings; photographic print; Bowman, Major; Burns, Lieut.; Sullivan, Lieut.; Student Army Training Corps
  - SATC (Student Army Training Core) marching to mess, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01156; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
  - Men outside military headquarters, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01157; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
  - First instructions from the Major, October 15, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01158; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
  - Blackie Thorn, Top Seargent - Co. B, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01159; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
    photographic print; Thorn, "Blackie"; Student Army Training Corps
  - Freshman company going to Drill, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01160; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
  - Major Bowman and staff marching in Armistice Day Parade, November 11, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01161; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
    photographic print; Bowman, Major; Student Army Training Corps
  - Inspection of SATC clothes, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01162; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
  - The Gobs rom the USS Paige marching in Armistice Day Parade, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01163; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
    Dan Prescott - Color Sgt.
    photographic print; Prescott, Dan; Student Army Training Corps
  - SATC at attention after Mess, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01164; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
  - Unidentified member of SATC, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01165; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
  - Typical room of Tufts student, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01166; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
  - SATC soldiers posing for pictures, November, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01167; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
  - SATC soldiers, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01168; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
    Rockie, Al Redway, Dick Bennet, Lawrence Haskins
    photographic print; Haskins, Lawrence; Rockie; Redway, Al; Bennet, Dick; Student Army Training Corps
  - SATC Private Pratt, Christmas, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01169; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
    photographic print; Pratt, Daniel; Student Army Training Corps
  - SATC Private Lawrence Haskins, Christmas, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01170; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
    Lawrence Haskins
    photographic print; Haskins, Lawrence; Student Army Training Corps
  - Goddard Gym during peace time, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01171; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
  - SATC Squad 24, Co. B, November, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01172; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
  - SATC Squad 24, Co. B, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01173; Haskins, Lawrence (Box Shared 106)
    People; photographic print; Student Army Training Corps
  - View of West Somerville from Ballou Hall, 1870; UA136.002.DO.01174; Unknown (Box Shared 106)
  - Old Brickyard on College Ave., 1890; UA136.002.DO.01176; Unknown (Box Shared 107)
  - Powder House, June 9, 1924; UA136.002.DO.01177; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
  - Students, 1900; UA136.002.DO.01178; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
  - Model T loaded with freshmen, September 4, 1940; UA136.002.DO.01179; Frieze, H.R. (Box Shared 108)
  - Students, 1886; UA136.002.DO.01181; Hardy (Box Shared 107)
  - Electron microscope, 1965; UA136.002.DO.01183; Duette (Box Shared 107)
    Students; People; Faculty; photographic print; Milburn, Nancy; Dept. of Biology
  - Freshmen warning poster, 1920; UA136.002.DO.01184; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
  - Students speaking with Dean Alvin R. Schmidt, Jr., 1965; UA136.002.DO.01191; Duette (Box Shared 107)
    Mekhel Saks, Charles Jordan, Dean Alvin Schmidt, Jr., Gregg Kuelin
    Faculty; Students; photographic print; Schmidt, Alvin Jr.; Kuelin, Gregg; Saks, Mekhel; Jordan, Charles
  - Six freshmen at registration, 1962; UA136.002.DO.01192; Unknown (Box Shared 107)
    Bob Yarmintino, Dave Boschetto, Dick Johnson, Mark Luster, Manny Cacciola, Bob Snyder, Paul Godfrey
    Students; People; photographic print; Godfrey, Paul; Yarmintino, Bob; Boschetto, Dave; Johnson, Dick; Luster, Mark; Cacciola, Manny; Snyder, Bob; Godfrey, Paul
  - Unidentified instructor, 1980; UA136.002.DO.01193; Unknown (Box Shared 107)
    Faculty; photographic print
  - Candle lighting ceremony during Alumni Weekend, 1985; UA136.002.DO.01194; Unknown (Box Shared 107)
    Alumni and alumnae; People; photographic print
  - President Hamilton and Faculty in Goddard Chapel, 1880; UA136.002.DO.01197; Stebbins, N.L. (Box Shared 107)
    Faculty; College presidents; photographic print; Hamilton, Frederick William
  - Instructing dental technicians in the Department of Social Dentistry, 1960; UA136.002.DO.01200; Magna Film Productions (Box Shared 107)
    5x9
    People; Faculty; Students; photographic print; School of Dental Medicine
  - A coed dorm scene in, 1974; UA136.002.DO.01201; Unknown (Box Shared 107)
    Dormitories; photographic print; Coll. of Liberal Arts & Jackson College
  - Irving Tomlinson, T.D.S, 1888; UA136.002.DO.01205; Hastings (Box Shared 108)
    photographic print; Tomlinson, Irving
  - Tufts band member, 1960; UA136.002.DO.01206; Unknown (Box Shared 109)
  - Tufts band member and drum, 1960; UA136.002.DO.01207; Duette (Box Shared 109)
  - Arthur Michael Chemistry Laboratory, 1965; UA136.002.DO.01210; Atlantic Photo Service (Box Shared 109)
  - Organic chemistry research area, Michael Laboratory, 1967; UA136.002.DO.01211; Unknown (Box Shared 109)
  - Student nurses in rehibilitation program, 1945; UA136.002.DO.01212; Duette (Box Shared 109)
    Students; photographic print; Boston School of Occupational Therapy
  - Student nurses in occupational therapy, 1945; UA136.002.DO.01213; Fay Foto Service, Inc. (Box Shared 109)
    Charlotte Bone, B.S.O.T. and Caroline Hausermann, B.S.O.T.
    Students; photographic print; Hausermann, Caroline; Bone, Charlotte; Boston School of Occupational Therapy
  - Brain dissection in neuroanatomy class, 1960; UA136.002.DO.01214; Duette (Box Shared 109)
  - Students studying brain, 1968; UA136.002.DO.01215; Duette (Box Shared 109)
  - Playing pool as occupational therapy, 1947; UA136.002.DO.01216; Keller, Robert J. (Box Shared 109)
    photographic print; Boston School of Occupational Therapy
  - Large Animal Hospital, Tufts University School of Veterinary Medicine, no date, UA136.002.DO.01217; Unknown (Box Shared 109)
    Buildings; photographic print; School of Veterinary Medicine
  - Horse's hoof being examined in the equine ward at Tufts University School of Veterinary Medicine's Large Animal Hospital, 1980; UA136.002.DO.01218; Unknown (Box Shared 109)
    Dr. Henry Valdez and Kathy Cellucci
    People; Animals; Horses; Students; photographic print; Cellucci, Kathy; Valdez, Dr. Henry; School of Veterinary Medicine
  - Soldier during World War I, 1914 -- 1918; UA136.002.DO.01219; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    Students; World War, 1914-1918; photographic print
  - Drafting classes for women, 1914 -- 1918; UA136.002.DO.01220; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
  - Mess Hall in Curtis Hall, 1914 -- 1918; UA136.002.DO.01221; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    Buildings; World War, 1914-1918; photographic print
  - Soldiers marching on Tufts campus, 1914 -- 1918; UA136.002.DO.01222; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    World War, 1914-1918; photographic print
  - Jackson students forming for Armistice Parade, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01223; Unknown (Box Shared 109)
    Student activities; World War, 1914-1918; photographic print; Jackson College
  - SATC Band, 1914 -- 1918; UA136.002.DO.01224; Unknown (Box Shared 109)
  - Representative of the SATC uniforms, 1914 -- 1918; UA136.002.DO.01225; Unknown (Box Shared 109)
  - Elton Killam, bugler, 1914 -- 1918; UA136.002.DO.01226; Unknown (Box Shared 109)
    Elton Killam
    Students; World War, 1914-1918; photographic print; Killam, Elton
  - YMCA at the balcony of Goddard Gymnasium, 1914 -- 1918; UA136.002.DO.01227; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    Buildings; World War, 1914-1918; photographic print; YMCA
  - Mr. Moeller, YMCA Director, 1914 -- 1918; UA136.002.DO.01228; Unknown (Box Shared 109)
    R. Moeller, YMCA Director
    People; World War, 1914-1918; photographic print; YMCA
  - Tufts biology lab in Harpswell, Maine, 1900; UA136.002.DO.01233; Unknown (Box Shared 109)
  - Fred Dayton Lambert, Professor of Botany, and his wife, Mary Anna "Polly" Ingalls, 1900; UA136.002.DO.01234; Unknown (Box Shared 109)
    Faculty; photographic print; Lambert, Fred D.; Lambert, Mary Anna "Polly" Ingalls
  - Strike Center on Medford campus, 1970; UA136.002.DO.01237; Morrow Christopher W. (Box Shared 109)
  - Student protest march, October 15, 1969; UA136.002.DO.01238; Young, Donald T. (Box Shared 109)
  - Marjorie Keller speaks at first strike meeting after death of students at Kent State University, 1970; UA136.002.DO.01239; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    Student activities; photographic print; Keller, Marjorie
  - Student protest, October, 1969; UA136.002.DO.01240; Young, Donald T. (Box Shared 109)
  - Students marching in protest of Vietnam War, October, 1969; UA136.002.DO.01241; Young, Donald T. (Box Shared 109)
    Students; Vietnamese Conflict, 1961-75; photographic print
  - Student protest, 1969; UA136.002.DO.01242; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    People; Students; Vietnamese Conflict, 1961-75; photographic print
  - Student protest march, 1969; UA136.002.DO.01243; Young, Donald T. (Box Shared 109)
  - Protest placards, 1969; UA136.002.DO.01244; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    Vietnamese Conflict, 1961-75; photographic print
  - Student protesters in front of Ballou Hall, 1969; UA136.002.DO.01245; Unknown (Box Shared 109)
    Students; People; Vietnamese Conflict, 1961-75; photographic print
  - Mayoralty campaign, 1956; UA136.002.DO.01246; Unknown (Box Shared 109)
    Events; Mayoralty; People; Students; photographic print
  - Plu Beta, 1943; UA136.002.DO.01248; Shearer, Gordon (Box Shared 109)
  - The Fourth Tufts College Orchestra, 1883 -- 1884; UA136.002.DO.01251; Folsom, A.H. (Box Shared 57)
    Student activities; Students; People; photographic print; Orchestra
  - Tufts students boarding bus for march in Washington, D.C., 1967; UA136.002.DO.01252; Unknown (Box Shared 57)
  - Student meeting in front of President Hallowell's house, Spring, 1968; UA136.002.DO.01253; Unknown (Box Shared 57)
    Students; People; College presidents; photographic print; Hallowell, Burton Crosby
  - John Baronian, football player, 1949; UA136.002.DO.01255; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    Athletics; Football; People; Students; photographic print; Baronian, John
  - John Baronian, 1949; UA136.002.DO.01256; Davis, Dwight (Box Shared 108)
  - Thomas Murnane and John Baronian, 1970; UA136.002.DO.01257; Levenson, Allen (Box Shared 108)
    Alumni and alumnae; College administrators; People; photographic print; Baronian, John; Murnane, Thomas
  - J. Baronian, B. Wolff, R. Goldstein, T. Horgan at Homecoming Kickoff, October 28, 1977; UA136.002.DO.01258; Livingston, June (Box Shared 57)
    Alumni and alumnae; People; photographic print; Baronian, John; Horgan, Timothy; Goldstein, Dr. Ralph H.; Wolff, Bob
  - John Baronian, marshal at commencement ceremonies, 1975; UA136.002.DO.01259; Unknown (Box Shared 57)
    Commencement; photographic print; Baronian, John
  - Edwin M. Schur, Chairman of Sociology Department, September 31, 1966; UA136.002.DO.01261; Duette (Box Shared 108)
    Faculty; People; photographic print; Schur, Edwin; Dept. of Sociology
  - Students experimenting with electricity, 1950; UA136.002.DO.01264; Unknown (Box Shared 57)
    Academic; photographic print
  - Alan Okolotowicz experimenting with polymers, 1970; UA136.002.DO.01265; Unknown (Box Shared 57)
    Academic; photographic print; Okolotowicz, Alan
  - Street marker for Medford/Somerville city line, 1965; UA136.002.DO.01267; Unknown (Box Shared 57)
  - Acting President William L. Hooper, March 3, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01268; Unknown (Box Shared 57)
    photo copy of painting of Acting President William L. Hooper
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Hooper, William Leslie
  - President Elmer Hewitt Capen, 1900; UA136.002.DO.01269; Unknown (Box Shared 57)
    photo copy of painting of President Elmer Hewitt Capen
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Capen, Elmer Hewitt
  - Engineering students in topography class, Fall, 1900; UA136.002.DO.01273; Unknown (Box Shared 57)
    People; Students; photographic print; College of Engineering
  - First class of women in engineering, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01274; Unknown (Box Shared 57)
    Academic; photographic print; College of Engineering
  - Parade on commencement day, 1950; UA136.002.DO.01275; Duette (Box Shared 57)
    Commencement; photographic print
  - Student participants in Tufts' Centennial Pageant, 1952; UA136.002.DO.01276; Hotel Photo Service (Box Shared 57)
    Joseph Costanza, Diana Manfield, James Walch, Walter Tengelson, Nancy Nutter
    Student activities; photographic print; Tengelson, Walter; Costanza, Joseph; Mansfield, Diana; Walch, James
  - Charles Tufts, founder of Tufts College, 1850; UA136.002.DO.01278; Hale's Photograph Rooms; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 108)
    copy negative credited to Rollins (box: "Tufts People")
    People; photographic print; Tufts, Charles
  - Hosea Ballou II, first president of Tufts College, 1870; UA136.002.DO.01279; Unknown (Box Shared 57)
    photo copy of painting of President Hosea Ballou
    People; photographic print; Ballou, Hosea, 2d
  - Dolbear's exhibit at the Crystal Palace Exhibition, 1882; UA136.002.DO.01280; Unknown (Box Shared 57)
    photographic print; Dolbear, Amos Emerson
  - Professor Fay on mountain climbing trip, 1922; UA136.002.DO.01281; Unknown
    From Munro collection.
    Faculty; Mountains; Fay, Charles Ernest
  - Home of Charles Tufts on Washington St., Somerville, 1900; UA136.002.DO.01282; Unknown (Box Shared 110)
  - Charles Tufts, 1839; UA136.002.DO.01283; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    photo copy of painting of Charles Tufts by S. Harrington
  - Mrs. Hannah Robinson Tufts, 1860; UA136.002.DO.01284; Hale's Photograph Rooms; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 108)
    Hannah Robinson Tufts, wife of Charles Tufts, copy negative credited to Rollins (box: "Tufts People")
    People; photographic print; Tufts, Hannah Robinson
  - Mrs. Hannah Robinson Tufts, 1839; UA136.002.DO.01285; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    photo copy of painting of Mrs. Hannah Robinson Tufts by S. Harrington
  - Professor Fay in scenic location, 1920; UA136.002.DO.01286; Unknown (Box Shared 110)
    Professor Fay
    Faculty; photographic print; Fay, Professor
  - Senator J.F. Kennedy and Dr. Nils Wessell, June, 1954; UA136.002.DO.01287; Duette (Box Shared 110)
    Senator John F. Kennedy and Dr. Nils Wessell
    People; Commencement; photographic print; Wessell, Nils Yngve; Kennedy, John F.
  - Acting President George Miller, 1940; UA136.002.DO.01291; Unknown (Box Shared 110)
    People; Faculty; photographic print; Miller, George Stewart
  - Commencement address, 1970; UA136.002.DO.01292; Young, Donald T. (Box Shared 108)
  - Commencement, 1960; UA136.002.DO.01293; Duette (Box Shared 110)
  - Commencement, 1961; UA136.002.DO.01294; Duette (Box Shared 110)
    Commencement; Students; Events; photographic print; Jackson College
  - Commencement, 1978; UA136.002.DO.01296; Herwig, Ellis (Box Shared 110)
  - Major Bowman of SATC, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01297; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    World War, 1914-1918; photographic print; Bowman, Major; Student Army Training Corps
  - SATC sleeping quarters, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01298; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    World War, 1914-1918; photographic print; Student Army Training Corps
  - President Hermon C. Bumpus, 1920; UA136.002.DO.01299; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
    President and Trustee Hermon C. Bumpus
    People; photographic print; Bumpus, Hermon Carey
  - President Hermon C. Bumpus, 1920; UA136.002.DO.01300; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
  - President Jean Mayer receiving ovation at Commencement, May, 1983; UA136.002.DO.01301; Unknown (Box Shared 110)
    President Jean Mayer
    People; Commencement; photographic print; Mayer, Jean
  - President Jean Mayer at Commencement, May, 1982; UA136.002.DO.01302; Unknown (Box Shared 110)
  - Hank Azaria and Jenny Langsan Cecile in costume, 1985; UA136.002.DO.01303; Levenson, Allen (Box Shared 108)
    Hank Azaria and Jenny Langsan Cecile
    Theater; photographic print; Azaria, Hank; Cecile, Jenny Langsan
  - Tufts Arena Theater, 1970; UA136.002.DO.01304; Mavin, John (Box Shared 108)
    Theater; photographic print
  - Tom Wolfe, 1978; UA136.002.DO.01305; Baer, J.C. (Box Shared 108)
    Tom Wolfe
    People; photographic print; Wolfe, Tom
  - The Amalgamates, 1988; UA136.002.DO.01306; Thornton, Dan (Box Shared 108)
    Student activities; photographic print; Amalgamates
  - Performers in the musical production of "Hair,", 1985; UA136.002.DO.01307; Unknown (Box Shared 110)
  - Production of the musical "Hair,", 1985; UA136.002.DO.01308; McGash, Ken (Box Shared 110)
  - Breaking soil for war garden, April 26, 1918; UA136.002.DO.01309; Unknown (Box Shared 108)
  - Class of 1913, UA136.002.DO.01310; Lewis, Thomas (Box Shared 108)
    3x7
  - Check out the knees!, 1960; UA136.002.DO.01311; Duette (Box Shared 110)
  - Robert F. Kennedy and unidentified men, 1960; UA136.002.DO.01312; Unknown (Box Shared 110)
    Robert F. Kennedy and unidentified men
    People; photographic print; Kennedy, Robert F.
  - Arthur Rubenstein, honorary degree recipient, 1964; UA136.002.DO.01313; Duette (Box Shared 110)
    Arthur Rubenstein
    Commencement; photographic print; Rubenstein, Arthur
  - Lyndon B. Johnson, commencement speaker, 1963; UA136.002.DO.01314; Duette (Box Shared 110)
    Lyndon B. Johnson
    Commencement; photographic print; Johnson, Lyndon Baines
  - A commencement kiss, 1964; UA136.002.DO.01315; Duette (Box Shared 110)
  - Real Admiral J.C. Wylie addresses Tufts Naval ROTC aborad USS Constitution, 1969; UA136.002.DO.01316; Lloyd, PH3 George D., USN (Box Shared 110)
    Rear Admiral J.C. Wylie
    Navy; NROTC; photographic print; Wylie, Rear Admiral J.C.
  - Student particpants at Commencement, 1970; UA136.002.DO.01317; Young, Donald T. (Box Shared 110)
    Commencement; Events; People; Students; photographic print
  - Seniors receiving their diplomas at Commencement, 1972; UA136.002.DO.01318; Morrow Christopher W. (Box Shared 110)
    Commencement; People; Students; Events; photographic print
  - Lawyer William Kuntsler speaking at Commencement, 1972; UA136.002.DO.01319; Morrow Christopher W. (Box Shared 110)
    William Kuntsler
    Commencement; photographic print; Kuntsler, William
  - Commencement, 1970; UA136.002.DO.01320; Unknown (Box Shared 110)
  - Dental assistant graduates and new moms, 1958; UA136.002.DO.01321; Unknown (Box Shared 110)
  - Commencement, 1966; UA136.002.DO.01322; Duette (Box Shared 110)
  - Graduate standing beside The Cannon, 1965; UA136.002.DO.01323; Unknown (Box Shared 110)
  - Professors at Commencement, 1976; UA136.002.DO.01324; Unknown (Box Shared 110)
  - Parents eating in cafeteria during Family Day, 1957; UA136.002.DO.01325; Duette (Box Shared 58)
  - 1912 Model T Ford used by Theta Delta Chi, October 1, 1940; UA136.002.DO.01328; Unknown (Box Shared 59)
    3x3
    Student activities; photographic print; Theta Chi
  - Fraternity brothers of Theta Delta Chi, 1965; UA136.002.DO.01329; Unknown (Box Shared 59)
  - Theta Delta Chi seniors, 1965; UA136.002.DO.01331; Unknown (Box Shared 58)
  - George Ekman and David Reick, Society of Scholars, Fall, 1969; UA136.002.DO.01333; Duette (Box Shared 59)
    George Ekman, David Reick
    Student activities; photographic print; Reick, David; Ekman, George; Society of Scholars
  - Members of Sigma Nu, 1960; UA136.002.DO.01334; Unknown (Box Shared 59)
    Student activities; photographic print; Sigma Nu
  - Members of the Geology Department, 1950; UA136.002.DO.01337; Unknown (Box Shared 59)
    Academic; Faculty; People; photographic print; Dept. of Geology
  - Associate Professor of Geology James D. Hume, 1950; UA136.002.DO.01338; Unknown (Box Shared 59)
    Faculty; People; Portraits; photographic print; Hume, Dr. James D.; Dept. of Geology
  - Geology trip with Professor Robert Nichols, January 25, 1940; UA136.002.DO.01339; Unknown (Box Shared 59)
    Students; People; Faculty; photographic print; Nichols, Robert L.; Dept. of Geology
  - Robin B. Wallace at Gallery 11, 1964; UA136.002.DO.01340; Unknown (Box Shared 59)
    Students; People; photographic print; Wallace, Robin Boysen
  - President Wessell and alumi at 25th anniversary celebration, 1955; UA136.002.DO.01341; Duette (Box Shared 58)
    Date approximate.
    Alumni and alumnae; People; College presidents; photographic print; Wessell, Nils Yngve
  - Wedding at Tufts, 1955; UA136.002.DO.01342; Duette (Box Shared 58)
    Events; People; photographic print
  - Newly elected members of the Tufts Alumni Council, 1963; UA136.002.DO.01343; Duette (Box Shared 58)
    (l to r) Edward Shea, Professor Elizabeth A. Weiant, Antonio de Jesus Cardozo, Catharine Stevens, Dr. Emmanuel Dutsch, Deborah Phillips
    Alumni and alumnae; People; photographic print; Phillips, Deborah; Shea, Edward J.; Weiant, Elizabeth A.; Cardozo, Antonio de Jesus; Deutsch, Dr. Emmanuel; Phillips, Deborah; Stevens, Catharine; Alumni Council
  - Wilbert Carter, Professor of Sociology and Anthropology, 1960; UA136.002.DO.01344; Unknown (Box Shared 59)
    Wilbert Carter
    Faculty; People; photographic print; Carter, Wilbert; Dept. of Sociology and Anthropology
  - Seymour O. Simches, John Wade Professor and Chairman of the Department of Romance Languages, 1960; UA136.002.DO.01345; Unknown (Box Shared 58)
    Seymour O. Simches
    Faculty; photographic print; Simches, Seymour O.; Dept. of Romance Languages
  - Dr. Melvin M. Ketchel, Professor of Physiology at Tufts School of Medicine, 1970; UA136.002.DO.01348; Unknown (Box Shared 58)
    Dr. Melvin M. Ketchel
    Faculty; People; photographic print; Ketchel, Dr. Melvin M.; School of Medicine
  - Physics - Impedence Bridge, March 26, 1936; UA136.002.DO.01349; Unknown (Box Shared 58)
    Academic; People; Students; photographic print; Dept. of Physics
  - Jackson College trio performing "Spring Festival,", 1940; UA136.002.DO.01351; Unknown (Box Shared 58)
    Eleanor R. Mulligan, Audrey Ross, Jean Mackenzie
    Student activities; photographic print; Mackenzie, Jean; Mulligan, Eleanor; Ross, Audrey
  - Men's boxing team, 1900; UA136.002.DO.01352; Unknown (Box Shared 59)
    Athletics; Boxing; photographic print
  - Arts festival on campus, 1985; UA136.002.DO.01356; McGash, Ken (Box Shared 59)
  - Student Senate meeting, 1985; UA136.002.DO.01357; Bashell, Steven (Box Shared 59)
  - Students on the Wessell Library roof, 1985; UA136.002.DO.01358; Bashell, Steven (Box Shared 58)
  - T Metro festivities, 1980; UA136.002.DO.01359; Pearlman, Jon (Box Shared 59)